{
    "subject": "resource/1953_Dutch_Grand_Prix",
    "predicate": "ontology/poleDriverTeam",
    "object": "resource/Scuderia_Ferrari",
    "human_readable": "The pole driver team for the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix is Scuderia Ferrari.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9833600521087646,
            "question": "Who was the pole driver team for the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9812955260276794,
            "question": "For which Grand Prix did Scuderia Ferrari secure pole position in 1953?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9696282744407654,
            "question": "What team was in pole position at the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9375911355018616,
            "question": "What was the name of the racing team that achieved pole position at the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8912092447280884,
            "question": "Which racing team participated in the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8843008875846863,
            "question": "In what year did Scuderia Ferrari compete in the Dutch Grand Prix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8769025206565857,
            "question": "Name the team that led the qualifying session for the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7679377794265747,
            "question": "Which racing team dominated the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix qualifying?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6982030272483826,
            "question": "Who held the top spot in qualifying for the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4236946403980255,
            "question": "Scuderia Ferrari is associated with what type of motorsport?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The pole driver team for the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix is Scuderia Ferrari.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6351_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who held the top spot in qualifying for the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6351_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which racing team dominated the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix qualifying?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6351_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the team that led the qualifying session for the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6351_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6351_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6351_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6351_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6351_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6351_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6351_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6351_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6351_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6351_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6351_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the answer in a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention that in the 1953 World Championship of Drivers, which was run to Formula Two rules, the four factory 500s all secured top six places with Alberto Ascari on pole position. This information suggests that Scuderia Ferrari had a strong presence and Ascari took pole position for the team.\n\nTherefore, based on this context, the statement \"The pole driver team for the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix is Scuderia Ferrari\" is supported by the provided documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context clearly indicates that Scuderia Ferrari dominated and won the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix with their drivers taking multiple positions in the podium, confirming that Scuderia Ferrari was indeed the pole driver team for the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}